responsemagic.com 2010-12-18

# Email Marketing System | Email Marketing Software | Email Responder | Auto Responder | Email Deliverabiliy

Platinum Synergy realizes that you care how your information is processed and shared, and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our Privacy Policy. By visiting our website ([www.platinumsynergy.com](http://www.platinumsynergy.com/)), as well as our associated websites [www.responsemagic.com](http://www.responsemagic.com/) , [www.synergyroom.com](http://www.synergyroom.com/) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

Any personal information provided or acquired by Platinum Synergy is controlled primarily by Platinum Synergy Group Inc., 10 Washburn Drive, Unit #4, Kitchener, Ontario N2R 1S2 hereinafter referred to as Platinum Synergy. 

Platinum Synergy recognizes the importance of respecting the privacy of those who visit our website and choose to take advantage of the services we offer. 

We believe it is important for you, our Customer, to know how we treat the information about you which we receive during your visits to our site. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, disclose, and safeguard the aggregate information we receive when you visit and browse our website. We encourage you to take the time to read this Privacy Policy as well as those of any other sites you visit, whether through a link on that site or otherwise. 

THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES ONLY TO THIS SITE, AND DATA ACQUIRED ONLINE. IT IS A PART OF THE SITE'S TERMS OF USE. 

Platinum Synergy guarantees to use and process your private information within the scope and purpose stated in the Terms of Service. 

Platinum Synergy uses commercially reasonable precautions to keep all disclosed personal information secure. Information collected through tracking and registration will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose without your express consent, except as provided in this Privacy Policy, or in a contract between Platinum Synergy and individual customers. 

When you visit our website, we receive may collect two types of information: (1) Site Use Information and Cookies, and (2) personal information you knowingly choose to disclose which is collected on individual bases. 

**Site Use Information**

Our servers automatically collect site use information, each time you visit our site. 

The site use information includes, but is not limited to, the following: the domain names, operating system in use (e.g. Macintosh, Windows), browser (e.g. Netscape, Internet Explorer) and version, the website which referred you to us, and other similar information. This information may be aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on our website, pages viewed, time and date of visits, and other similar information. We may use and disclose site use information, for example, to measure the use of our website, improve the content, explain the utility of our website and services we provide, and to extend their functionality. 

Information we collect may be used to enhance your use of our website, and to provide you with a service that you ordered, arrange the website in the most customer friendly way, communicate special offers and featured items, and/or respond to your questions and suggestions. 

Platinum Synergy only collects personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily registering to our service. 

In the case of an agreement, personal information includes data that identifies you as the specific individual, i.e. your name, email address, phone number, geographical address, and/or company name and address. This information is used to complete the account application process, customer's information request, and/or to verify the validity of the request, and to proceed with payment. 

Information will be used solely for proceeding payments for services that you ordered. 

**Mailing Policy**

When you send us an email, we use your email address to thank you for your comment and/or reply to your question, and we will store your communication and our reply for any future correspondence. Beyond our initial reply, we will never use your email address to send you any unsolicited message or information unless explicitly requested, nor will we share it with or sell it to anyone else for such use. 

When you request information or other services from us, we use your email address and any other information you give us to provide you with the information or other services you requested, until you ask us to stop (using the 'unsubscribe' instructions provided with each email, and/or on the site where you signed up, and/or as we otherwise provide), or until the information or service is no longer available. We will not use your address or other information to provide you with any unsolicited messages or information (unless that is part of the service you are requesting), nor will we share it with or sell, rent or lease it to any third party for such use. 

**Response Magic Contact and Opt Out Policy**

The contact information contained within the Response Magic accounts of our customers is private and confidential.  We do not share or sell contact information to Response Magic users. 

Each contact within a Response Magic account may Opt Out of receiving the emails being sent to them by the Response Magic account owner at any time.  Each email sent by Response Magic to a recipient contains a link at the bottom which allows for the recipient to Opt Out of receiving emails.  In addition, the recipient can choose to opt out of all future emails by either that sender's Response Magic account or globally.  If the contact chooses to opt out globally, the email address they provide will be blocked by our system completely, meaning that no Response Magic user can add that email address to their system at any time in the future. 

To globally opt out, please fill out the form found [here](http://www.responsemagic.com/optout.php)

Opt Outs are handled on an email address basis.  If a recipient opts out, they will only be opting out to receive emails to that specific email address. 

Opt Out requests can only be reversed pending contact from the opted-out recipient from the email address that was removed.  

**Your Customer's Private Information Policy**

Platinum Synergy recognizes the importance of respecting the privacy of those who decided to entrust their sensitive information with you. We assure to make every effort to safeguard their security. Platinum Synergy will never use the information about the customers you collect within our services to send any unsolicited messages or information, nor will we share it with or sell it to anyone else for such use. 

**Cookies**

Similar to other commercial websites, the technology called "cookies" may be used to provide you with tailored information. A cookie is a small piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. You may be able to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Our cookies collect general information that enhances our ability to serve you and measure the utility of our website. 

**Information Security**

We believe that keeping personal information secure is one of our most significant responsibilities. We restrict access to Personal Information about you to those employees and others who need to know that information to assist us in our business, or to provide products or services to you. We safeguard personal information, according to established security standards and procedures, by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards for the information. 

When we request customers to enter sensitive information (such as the credit card number), it is encrypted and protected with the best encryption software in the industry -- SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon at the bottom of web browsers, such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

All of our customers' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk, or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
